{
    "subject": "resource/A_Million_Ways_to_Die_in_the_West",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Albert Takes a Trip",
    "human_readable": "The title of A Million Ways to Die in the West is 'Albert Takes a Trip'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9595325589179993,
            "question": "Who takes a trip in A Million Ways to Die in the West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9207684993743896,
            "question": "What is the title of A Million Ways to Die in the West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310933113098145,
            "question": "Where is A Million Ways to Die in the West set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8255418539047241,
            "question": "What is the subtitle of A Million Ways to Die in the West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7843582034111023,
            "question": "What is the genre of A Million Ways to Die in the West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.703736424446106,
            "question": "Is A Million Ways to Die in the West a popular film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6906872391700745,
            "question": "Who directed A Million Ways to Die in the West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6709684729576111,
            "question": "What year was A Million Ways to Die in the West released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6688438057899475,
            "question": "Does A Million Ways to Die in the West feature Will Ferrell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5961309671401978,
            "question": "Is A Million Ways to Die in the West a comedy film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of A Million Ways to Die in the West is 'Albert Takes a Trip'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7883_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does A Million Ways to Die in the West feature Will Ferrell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7883_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was A Million Ways to Die in the West released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7883_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed A Million Ways to Die in the West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7883_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7883_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is my evaluation:\n\nSince \"The title of A Million Ways to Die in the West is 'Albert Takes a Trip'\" is not supported by the documents, I conclude that this triple is incorrect.\n\nSo, the output will be:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\nThis means that the title of the movie \"A Million Ways to Die in the West\" is actually different from what is stated in the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not support the statement that \"The title of A Million Ways to Die in the West is 'Albert Takes a Trip'.\" According to the documents, the actual title is \"A Million Ways to Die in the West,\" and it includes Albert Stark as a character but does not refer to his trip specifically as the title."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The title of A Million Ways to Die in the West is not \"Albert Takes a Trip\". The correct title, as provided in the context information, is \"A Million Ways to Die in the West\".",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context mentions the film's title as \"A Million Ways to Die in the West\".",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the title of A Million Ways to Die in the West was actually revealed as \"A Million Ways to Die in the West\" itself, not \"Albert Takes a Trip\", which implies that this fact is true and the alternative title is false.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The title of the film is explicitly stated as \"A Million Ways to Die in the West,\" not \"Albert Takes a Trip.\"",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}